We've been talking about comparatives how we can in detail describe the differences between things but
我们一直在谈论比较我们如何详细描述事物之间的差异，但是
I feel like before we really look at some examples of how to put all these things together we can very
我觉得在我们真正看一些如何将所有这些东西放在一起的例子之前，我们可以非常
quickly talk about superlatives superlatives like a superlative as when you have something that is either
快速谈论最高级 最高级就像最高级一样，当你有东西时
all the way at the top or all the way at the bottom.
一直在顶部或一直在底部。
OK it's not just more or less it's all the way up here or all the way down here.
好吧，这不仅仅是或多或少，它一直在这里或一直在这里。
So there used to kind of two compare.
所以曾经有两种比较。
You might compare something and then say that one is the for example most beautiful.
你可能会比较一些东西，然后说一个是最漂亮的。
This one is more beautiful.
这个更漂亮。
It's talking about these two things A is more beautiful than B and then A is the most beautiful.
就是说这两个东西A比B美，然后A最美。
That means not only is it more beautiful than B it's more beautiful than all other things to be in that
这意味着它不仅比 B 更美丽，而且比所有其他事物都更美丽
category.
类别。
OK.
好的。
So it follows the same rules that we learned before when we have one or two syllables then we'll add
所以它遵循我们之前学到的相同规则，当我们有一个或两个音节时，我们将添加
e s t est instead of her right for superlatives fastest funniest coolest boldest quietest.
最高级最快最有趣最酷最大胆最安静。
Right.
正确的。
But you could also hear for example say most quiet.
但是你也可以听到例如说最安静。
It's OK if you said most funny.
如果你说最有趣，那也没关系。
It's OK.
没关系。
It's also OK.
也没关系。
So in these cases you can do you can do both.
所以在这些情况下，你可以做你可以做。
And again you just need to pay attention to how these are used and which ones are more common.
同样，您只需要注意这些是如何使用的以及哪些更常见。
So then for these it's the same rule again three syllables or more.
那么对于这些​​，三个音节或更多音节也是同样的规则。
And sometimes two like these.
有时两个像这样。
So least experienced nothing is less than that.
因此，经验最少的事情就是这样。
It's the least experienced.
这是经验最少的。
OK.
好的。
We don't need to use it then because we're not comparing.
那时我们不需要使用它，因为我们没有比较。
We don't have to add then my brother is the least experienced maybe doctor I've ever met.
我们不必添加，那么我的兄弟可能是我见过的经验最少的医生。
Which would be very scary least fortunate.
不幸的是，这将是非常可怕的。
Again it's the lowest.
再次是最低的。
OK.
好的。
We're just using adjectives here fortunate experienced again these are three syllables or more and sometimes
我们只是在这里使用形容词幸运再次经历这些是三个音节或更多，有时
two syllables like this one for example we wouldn't say usually we wouldn't say bizarre list but we
像这样的两个音节 例如 我们不会说 通常我们不会说 bizarre list 但我们
would often say most bizarre.
常会说最离奇。
So the rule is the same for at least in most least as here most is here most bizarre most excited most
所以规则是相同的，至少在大多数情况下，至少在这里，最奇怪，最兴奋最
fortunate most experienced least experienced least fortunate least excited least.
幸运 最多 经验 最少 最少 幸运 最少 兴奋 最少。
Bizarre.
奇怪。
So pay attention when you're listening to movies or talking with people to whether or not for two syllable
所以在听电影或与人交谈时要注意是否为两个音节
words people are using more or they're using her or they're using est or they're using most or at least
人们使用更多或他们正在使用她或他们正在使用 est 或他们使用最多或至少使用的词
parts of pay attention to that.
部分注意那个。
And now let's look at some real examples of how we can sort of put all this together.
现在让我们看一些真实的例子，说明我们如何将所有这些放在一起。